Mar Bates

IT Technician

Vancouver, WA 98662 naje.bates@gmail.com (785)226-6677

Retired Military Veteran with over 23 years of proven experience in quality assurance, safety management, Six Sigma business improvement techniques, and project coordination, various duties, positions and responsibilities have allowed me to broaden my spectrum of knowledge, which led me to start a B.S. degree in Homeland Security and become a graduate from Clark college with a Network Technologies Degree.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Supervisor

Sapa Extrusions North America - Portland, OR February 2017 to March 2018

Supervised over 50 workers during the cleansing and painting of Extruded aluminum for various National and International corporations. Ensured safety, accountability and proper order of all personnel, product and equipment.

Staff Assistant Non-Commissioned Officer-In-Charge / Inspector Instructor / Platoon Sergeant/ Drill Sergeant

United States Army - World June 1998 to May 2014

NCO

United States Marines and Army June 1992 to May 1998

Education

Associate in Computer Networking

Clark College - Vancouver, WA March 2017 to June 2020

Skills

- microsoft (10+ years)
- Hazmat
- Leadership

- Computer Skills
- Time Management
- Training
- Instructor (10+ years)
- Management (10+ years)
- Resolution management (10+ years)
- Active Directory
- Linux
- · Computer Networking
- Network Administration
- LAN
- VMWare
- · Cloud Computing
- Information Security
- DNS
- Operating Systems
- Microsoft Windows
- Help Desk
- Microsoft Windows Server
- WAN
- TCP/IP
- DHCP
- computer networking (3 years)
- Network Monitoring
- Azure

Military Service

Branch: USMC/US Army Service Country: United States

Rank: SSG/SFC

June 1992 to May 2014

Additional Information

COMPUTER SKILLS

Microsoft Office Suite, Networking, A+, Computer Repair, Apple, Cisco systems(routers & switches), Cloud computing, Virtual computing, linux, Active Directory Server, Windows XP-10, Information Security, Printer set up and repair